edudemic.com 2017-12-16

# Terms & Privacy Policy | Edudemic

## Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for Use of Edudemic.com (Effective Date 1/5/2016)

Thank you for using Edudemic.com’s site content and services. This page will explain how we gather and employ different kinds of information to provide users with content and related products and services. By using our website, you are agreeing to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

Typically, we collect submitted information and automatic information. Data that users voluntarily submit through our web form is considered “submitted” information, which may be personal contact information and any other details that may be required to match users to an education product or service. This helps us provide the services requested by our visitors. We collect, store and share submitted information with schools and other third parties as necessary to provide users with information about education-related services, schools and programs.

By submitting this information, you authorize Edudemic.com and our affiliated schools and partners to contact you — in accordance with all applicable laws — by phone, text messages, email or mail regarding education options or related topics. If you receive any email communications from us, a school, or third party, you will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe through a link in the email, which will remove you from further mailings from that sender.

Edudemic.com also collects automatic information, certain types of anonymous information, whenever you interact with us. This information helps us make site improvements and create a tailored user experience. For example, we use “cookies” to collect anonymous data for analytics, site optimization and for tailored advertising and marketing purposes. Examples of this kind of information include, but are not limited to, your browser version, operating system version and your IP address.

By using our website, you acknowledge and agree that automatic information we collect may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties to provide information about degrees, programs and other education-related products and services. You also acknowledge and agree that we retain the right to release any collected information — including personally identifiable data — to businesses providing our company with administration services, such as an email delivery service. In addition, through this action, you grant us, our affiliates, partners and vendors the right to contact you for a period of time, and relinquish any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable law. Your submission serves as an omission to Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may exempt us from other applicable laws.

In addition, we retain the right to release your personal information in instances required by law. Examples of this include abiding by a subpoena or other legal procedure we believe is necessary to preserve our rights, ensure yours and others’ safety, identify alleged fraud, reply to a government or legal request and/or in the instance that Edudemic.com is merging, acquisitioning or selling some or all of its assets to a third party.

_It is possible that we will revise our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy in the future if we change our practices. We recommend that you reread this document periodically to stay current with our practices concerning your privacy and other important information._

## Edudemic.com’s Use of Cookies

By using this website, you acknowledge and consent to our use of cookies.

Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user’s web browser for technical purposes such as web analytics. We perform web analytics primarily using Google, Inc.’s Google Analytics. Advertising cookies do not contain personally identifiable information, which allows users to remain anonymous. However, they do permit advertisers to make ads more relevant to the user’s interests. Advertising cookies are sometimes referred to as third-party cookies because they track navigation and publish ads on behalf of third parties.

For more information about Google Analytics, check Google’s privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>.  
We — including activities through services and partnerships with vendors and third-party service providers — may use cookies for the following purposes:

  * Web analytics such as demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis
  * “Lead auditing” to ensure the accuracy, relevance and validity of submitted information
  * Marketing and conversion-tracking cookies for, but not limited to, targeting and optimizing digital ad serving to improve relevance, user experience and advertising effectiveness

You can remove cookies through your browser settings at any time, but note that you may need to do this on a per-use basis as opposed to a one-time basis. By visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website, you can opt out of receiving personalized ads from third-party advertisers and ad networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or that follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.
